centerparcs.co.uk 2018-09-02

# Privacy Policy | Center Parcs

Please read this privacy policy carefully as it sets out how Center Parcs in the UK and Ireland (when the Longford Forest Village opens), Aqua Sana and companies in the Center Parcs group (“Center Parcs”) use your personal information when you visit our website, make a booking, visit or supply a Center Parcs Village. 

In relation to the personal information we process about you, the data controllers within the Center Parcs group are listed in the Center Parcs group section below.

If you have any questions about this policy or do not agree with it, please contact us at [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk) or if you are resident in the Republic of Ireland, at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate.

This policy does not apply to employee personal information. For further information on how we handle employee personal information or to exercise any of your employee privacy rights, please contact us at [employee.dataprotection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:employee.dataprotection@centerparcs.co.uk).

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any changes. _ _ If we propose to make any material changes and you have an account with us, we will send you an email notifying you of such changes. Otherwise, we will display a notice on our website identifying the changes.

**What does this policy apply to?**

This policy applies to personal information we hold about you, however we obtain it. We collect information at different points during our relationship with you, for example, when you browse our website, create your account on the website, when you book a Center Parcs break or activities, when you are in our Villages, visit Aqua Sana, if you contact our Contact Centre, if you sign up to our marketing communications and if you enter any promotions or competitions that we run, and if you are a sole trader or partnership that provide goods or services to us.  

**Contents**

This policy contains the following information:

  * What information do we collect about you and why?
  * Marketing activities
  * Building profiles and targeting communications
  * Cookies and similar technologies
  * Who do we share your information with?
  * Where in the world do we hold your information?
  * How long do we keep your information?
  * How secure is your information?
  * What are your data protection rights?
  * How do you make a complaint?
  * The Center Parcs Group

**What information do we collect about you and why?**

We collect different information depending on what you want to do and how you interact with us. We need to tell you what we use your information for and the legal grounds we have to use it.

_**Information collected when you use Center Parcs maintained websites, social media or enter competitions**_

**Things you do**

| 

**What information is collected**

| 

**What is it used for**

| 

**Our Legal Grounds for collecting information**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Browse the website (cookies)

| 

Information about your computer, such as which browser you are using, your network location, the type of connection you are using (e.g. broadband, ADSL etc) and your IP address. This is done through cookies. See our Cookie Policy for more detail.

| 

Improving content and functionality on our website and to enable us to communicate with you.

| 

Legitimate interests of Center Parcs to improve its services.

In order to ensure that your rights are protected, we ensure that the level of information gathered is limited. We also ensure that this personal data is only used to determine if the website works well and to enable Center Parcs to improve its services.  
  
Searching for a break or spa break

| 

If you search for a break we will collect the following information:

· number of people on break;

· the Village you wish to stay at;

· arrival and departure dates;

· number and type of accommodation required; and

· whether adapted or dog lodges are preferred/required.

| 

All the information we request from you is needed in order to provide availability and pricing details in relation to your search.

| 

Taking steps at your request prior to entering into a contract.

To ensure we can complete the performance of our contract with you we require you to provide the stated information. We cannot fulfil your request or accept your booking without this information.  

Enter a competition

| 

If you enter a competition with us we will collect your name, email address, postal address and contact details. 

| 

Administration of the competition and to contact you if you have been successful.

| 

Legitimate interests of Center Parcs in running competitions and other promotions.  
  
Enter a competition and consent to receive marketing

| 

If you enter a competition and consent to receive marketing, we will collect your name, email address, postal address and contact details.

| 

Sending direct marketing communications to you.

| 

Consent.

You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.    
  
Marketing communications opt in

| 

If you sign up or request marketing communications we will as a minimum collect your full name and email address.

| 

Sending direct marketing communications to you and digital marketing advertisements. You can update these at any time through your account or via the unsubscribe link on all emails. 

| 

Consent

You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, although this may take up to 28 days to take effect.  

_**Information collected when you book a break and/or activities**_

**Things you do**

| 

**What information is collected**

| 

**What is it used for**

| 

**Our Legal Grounds for collecting information**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Booking a break or spa break

| 

If you book a break and/or activity, we need the following information as a minimum:

· your name;

· email address;

· postal address _;_

· telephone number and type;

· date of birth;

· details of other people and vehicles in your party;

· the Village you are staying at;

· arrival and departure dates;

· number and type of accommodation required including adapted or dog friendly;

\- type of activity and date required; and

· financial details for payment.

| 

All of the information we request from you is needed in order to book and provide your break.  We cannot provide your break without it.

If an adapted lodge is required the information is used to ensure that Center Parcs complies with its obligations under equality legislation, by ensuring you have access to our facilities that are suitable for your needs.

| 

Performance of a contract to provide your break or spa break.

To allow us to complete your booking we require you to provide the stated information.

We do not ask for further details of your specific requirements or disability unless you provide us with additional information so that we can make special arrangements during your break (including in relation to medical care).  
  
Registering for an account

| 

To book a break you will need to set up an account. To enable this we will need the following information as a minimum:

\- name

· email address (this cannot be used to create and log into multiple accounts);

· password; and

\- marketing communication preferences.

| 

All of the information we request from you is needed in order to set up your account. We cannot provide your break without it.

| 

Performance of a contract with you to provide your account.  
  
Pre-registration of guests on your break

| 

Details of party members are required but these can be reviewed and updated at any time up to arrival via your account. Information required includes:

· names and addresses of all members of your party;

\- email address (optional provision) for all members of your party;

· ages of all children in your party, if under 18 years; and

· vehicle registration number.

| 

This information is requested to provide for the safety and security of everyone on our Villages and to ensure we can identify all our guests, including for example any missing children.

| 

Legitimate interests of Center Parcs to ensure the safety of guests and employees in the Villages.  
  
_**Information collected when you visit our Villages.**_

**Things you do**

| 

**What information is collected**

| 

**What is it used for**

| 

**Our Legal Grounds for collecting information**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Booking Activities and taking part in activities

| 

When activities are booked whilst in the Village the following information is collected as a minimum:

· name;

· address;

· date of birth if under 18 years old;

· age if over 18;

·  lodge number;

· medical information relevant to the activity.

| 

This will be recorded into our central activity systems. It is needed in order to provide the activities that you want and ensure you are safe to do the activity.

We retain information about the lodge number for emergency contact purposes and to understand the patterns of transactions to improve the range of activities and facilities available to you whilst on a break.

| 

Performance of our contract with you and to comply with health and safety legislation (where applicable).

Legitimate Interests of Center Parcs to continue to offer better customer service.  
  
Booking Treatments

| 

When treatments are booked whilst in the spa the following information is collected as a minimum:

\- name;

· date of birth if under 18 years old;

· age if over 18;

· lodge number;

contact details;

\- medical information relevant to the activity.

| 

This will be recorded into the relevant systems. It is needed in order to provide the treatments that you want and ensure you are safe to receive the treatment.

| 

Performance of our contract with you and to comply with health and safety legislation (where applicable).  
  
Transactions On Village

| 

Records of retail and restaurant transactions. Data collected as a minimum:

\- total transaction value;

\- lodge number;

\- date and time; and

\- name of retail outlet or restaurant.

| 

We retain information about the total value, date, time and lodge number of a transaction to understand the patterns of transactions and to be able to use this information to improve the range of services and facilities available to you whilst on a break.

| 

Legitimate Interests of Center Parcs to enhance and develop the services and facilities available to guests.  
  
Security measures whilst on Village

| 

CCTV is in place across the Village to monitor and maintain safety of all guests and employees.

| 

We use CCTV footage to assist in monitoring and maintaining safety within our Villages and to prevent and detect crime.

Where necessary this footage may also be shared with the authorities for law enforcement purposes.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to ensure the safety of guests and employees in the Villages and to assist with law enforcement. 

This footage may also be used to exercise and defend our legal rights.  
  
| 

Body worn cameras may be used by our security team to capture images and audio in response to certain incidents in accordance with our Body Worn Camera Policy.

| 

This footage is used to assist in monitoring and maintaining safety within our Villages and to prevent and detect crime.

Where necessary this footage may also be shared with the authorities for law enforcement purposes.

Our security team will inform you before turning on their body worn cameras.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to ensure the safety of guests and employees in the Villages and to assist with law enforcement.

This footage may also be used to exercise and defend our legal rights.  
  
| 

Automatic Number Plate Recognition is in place on our Villages to ensure the safety and security of guests and employees.

| 

Automatic Number Plate Recognition (ANPR) systems are also used to assist in monitoring and maintaining safety within our Villages and to assist with law enforcement.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to ensure the safety of guests and employees in the Villages and to assist with law enforcement.

This footage may also be used to exercise and defend our legal rights.  
  
Attending Guest Services

| 

If you attend Guest Services in one of our Villages during your break to report an issue, fault or complaint the following information is collected, as a minimum:

· name;

· address;

· lodge number; and

· nature of enquiry.

| 

This information is used to resolve the enquiry, or progress a complaint as appropriate.

This will be recorded into the relevant recording systems.  The information is also used in case there is a complaint or claim about the break.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to provide customer services and provide you with an appropriate response to your query. 

We may also use this information in order to exercise and defend our legal rights.  
  
Contacting the Contact Centre

| 

If you contact our Contact Centre before, during or after your break the following information is collected, as a minimum:

· name;

· address;

· lodge number; and

· nature of enquiry.

| 

This information is used to resolve the enquiry, or progress a complaint as appropriate.

This will be recorded into the relevant recording systems.  The information is also used in case there is a legal claim about the break.

All call recordings are kept for a period of 7 years and then deleted in accordance with our retention policy.

| 

The legitimate Interests of Center Parcs to provide customer services and provide you with an appropriate response to your query. 

We may also use this information in order to exercise and defend our legal rights.  
  
Medical Assistance

| 

If you attend the Medical Centre in one of our Villages the following information is collected, as a minimum:

· name;

· address;

· lodge number; and

· medical condition or injury

| 

This will be recorded into our central medical systems and retained in accordance with our retention policy. It is required by law to register a record of attendance by a medical professional.

| 

Required by law and in order to exercise and defend our legal rights.  
  
On Village incidents

| 

Records of accidents and treatments received, security incidents and maintenance issues. The following information is collected as a minimum:

· name;

· address;

· date of birth if under 18 years old;

· age if over 18;

· lodge number; and

· medical information relevant to the activity.

| 

This information is used to resolve the enquiry or progress a complaint as appropriate.

We are required by law to keep a record of accidents and treatments.

The information is also used in case there is a claim about the cause of the accident and/or the treatments received.

| 

The legitimate Interests of Center Parcs to provide customer services and provide you with an appropriate response to your issue. 

We may also use this information in order to exercise and defend our legal rights and may be required by law to process this information.  
  
Using guest Wi-Fi on Village

| 

The following information is collected:

\- name; and

\- IP address and MAC address.

| 

The information is used to provide the Wi-Fi service to you.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to provide you with Wi-Fi across the Villages.   
  
Appearance in marketing material

| 

The following information is collected:

\- name;

\- contact details; and

\- age if under 18 years.

| 

The information is collected as we may need to contact you in the future.

| 

Consent and the legitimate interests of Center Parcs to create marketing materials.  
  
_**Information collected after your break**_

**Things you do**

| 

**What information is collected**

| 

**What is it used for**

| 

**Our Legal Grounds for collecting information**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Completing the Welcome Home Questionnaire

| 

If you complete a Welcome Home questionnaire the following information is collected as a minimum:

· name;

· address;

· lodge number; and

· your opinions related to the survey questions.

| 

This information is used to provide feedback to the relevant departments in each Village and to address an issue or complaint.

| 

Legitimate interests of Center Parcs to obtain feedback on your visit.

This is necessary to enable us to improve the services we provide and to ensure that you have the best possible experience when you visit Center Parcs.  
  
_**Information collected at other times**_

**Things you do**

| 

**What information is collected**

| 

**What is it used for**

| 

**Our Legal Grounds for collecting information**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Contacting Guest Services

| 

If you ring our Contact Centre to make an enquiry before booking a break the following information is collected, as a minimum:

· name;

· address; and

· nature of enquiry.

| 

This information is used to resolve the enquiry, or progress a complaint as appropriate.

This will be recorded into the relevant recording systems.  The information is also used in case there is a complaint or claim about the break.

The information will also be used to enable us to learn and continually improve the quality of the service or products we provide.

All call recordings are kept for a period of 7 years and then deleted in accordance with our retention policy.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to provide customer services and provide you with an appropriate response to your query. 

We may also use this information in order to exercise and defend our legal rights.  
  
Surveys / Questionnaires

| 

We may from time to time ask for you to complete a survey relating to something we are looking to implement or your feedback on Center Parcs services e.g. new technology or activities. If you choose to take part in a survey the following information may be collected, as a minimum:

· name;

· address;

· lodge number; and

· your opinions related to the survey questions. 

| 

This information is used to gather feedback on the subject matter and will be used to evaluate whether it is something which will be implemented across the Center Parcs group to improve services and the guest experience.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to contact our guests and to get feedback about a trial or promotion or activity etc. This is necessary to enable us to improve the services we provide and to ensure that guests have the best possible experience when they visit Center Parcs.  
  
_**Third Party Data**  
_

**Collection Points**

| 

**What third party information used**

| 

**What is it used for**

| 

**Our Legal Grounds for collecting information**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Other sources

| 

Lifestyle data from companies like Experian.

| 

We supplement the information we hold about you with data from other third-party sources such as Experian, to standardise, cleanse and correct the information we hold about you. This helps us keep our records cleansed , up to date and of the highest quality.

We also use third party data for example the Experian ConsumerView database, to enrich our data by looking at consumer demographics, consumption patterns and attitudes.  This allows us to continue to improve our products and services.

| 

The legitimate interests of Center Parcs to ensure the data quality.

This use is not detrimental to you as we only send relevant marketing materials to you, based on the information we know about you. Whether or not you receive the marketing information does not affect your ability to book a break or activity with us.

You have the right to withdraw your consent to receive marketing communications at any time.   
  
**Where Center Parcs' legal ground for processing is legitimate interests, you have a right to object to Center Parcs' use of this information. If you want to object, contact us at  [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk "Email"), or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate, _ _ or by phone on [0344 8267723](tel:03448267723 "Call").**

**Marketing activities**

So that you are the first to hear about our exciting new offers, activities and facilities, we may provide you with information through online digital services (e.g. online advertising, social media communications), or by direct marketing (e.g. phone, e-mail, text, post), unless you have asked us not to do so. 

When you book your break or spa break you have the option to opt out of our marketing communications. This is because, when we collect your contact details during the sale of a service, a law known as the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 (and in Ireland, the European Communities (Electronic Communications Networks and Services) (Privacy Electronic Communications) Regulations 2011) gives us the right to contact you for marketing purposes provided that we inform you that we intend to contact you and give you the opportunity to tell us that you would prefer not to hear from us. We want to make sure that we only contact people who do want to hear from us so you can opt-out at any time either during the booking journey, through every email we send you, by logging into your account and changing your preferences or, right now, by calling our Contact Centre on 03448 8267723.

Otherwise, we will only contact you for marketing purposes if you give us your consent to do so. You can change your mind at any time by following any of the options described above.

Please note that if you have a forthcoming booking we will send you service emails related to your break or spa break even when you have unsubscribed from marketing communications, as this is information you will require for your break or spa break.

We also use your personal information to tailor the marketing communications we send to you, or the things you see when you log into the account facility. 

We do not provide your personal information to external organisations (i.e. outside of Center Parcs) for their own marketing purposes.

**Building profiles and targeting communications**

When you interact with Center Parcs we collect information relating to your booking history with us for example the type of accommodation you choose and the activities you and the members of your party do. We use this information to build a profile or picture of the things you like and dislike, so that when we communicate with you we can send you personalised, relevant and timely communications, about things that may interest you.

We do this for two reasons. Firstly so that we can better understand our guests which helps us to improve your Center Parcs experience.  For example if you only come on breaks as a group of adults, we will not send you communications relating to activities for children.

The second reason we use profiling techniques is to better understand what our guests like doing. We want to understand what restaurants and activities you use so we can improve the guest experience.  For instance , if we find that only a small number of guests staying in lodges in the outer areas visit the Parc Market, this might indicate to us that our guests would benefit from the provision of another less central Parc Market.  Please be aware that, when we collect information about your activities, bookings and purchases on site, we will only link it to the lodge that you are staying in. This means that it is not linked to you directly but allows us to get an idea of what people booking the lodges of the kind you stayed in are likely to be interested in or missing out on during their visit. For example , if your group has booked numerous outdoor activities, we might send you communications about other outdoor activities that we think your group might be interested in.

As part of our profiling techniques, we will use third party lifestyle data to enrich our insight and understanding of guests’ interests and preferences. Such information is compiled using publicly available data about you, for example number of children, age of children, household income, these can be at a variety of levels from postcode area to individual households.

If you do not want us to use your personal information in this way we can only remove you from this by opting you out of all other marketing communications. If you wish to do this please contact us at [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk) or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate.   

**Cookies and other similar technologies**

We use cookies and other similar technologies (e.g. pixel tags or links) to remember you when you visit our websites and Apps and so we can improve your online experience to suit your needs. These help us understand how you and others use our websites and Apps, view our services and respond to our advertising, so we can tailor direct marketing and enhance our overall service offering. This also saves you from re-inputting information when you return to the websites or Apps.

When you receive direct marketing from us via email, we may use technology e.g. pixel tags or links to determine your use of and interest in our direct marketing.  For more information about the cookies and other similar technologies that we use, the purposes we use them for, and how to disable them, please visit our cookies policy.

**Who do we share this information with?**

Our group - your personal information may be shared with other companies within the Center Parcs group of companies based in the UK and Ireland because we operate centralised systems. We may also share your personal information with a purchaser or potential purchaser of our business but will always comply with the applicable data protection laws and keep your personal information secure.

Third parties - we may share your personal information with selected third parties.  Such as our suppliers, including businesses who provide IT services, operate activities in our Villages, our concession partners (i.e. the shops and restaurants operated by third parties within our Villages), property managers, printing and fulfilment agencies, marketing, research and communications agencies. Other third parties include our insurers, auditors and other professional advisers.

They only use the personal information we give them to provide their services. We only give them the personal information that they actually need in order to provide the services to us and all suppliers we engage are contractually required to ensure that they too comply with applicable data protection laws and keep your personal information secure.

Social media partners \- we share certain personal information about you with social media partners, such as Facebook and Twitter to participate in their Custom Audience and/or Lookalike Audience programs. This helps us to communicate with you more effectively and ensures that when you are on those platforms, you are more likely to see adverts about Center Parcs if you are likely to be interested in them. In order to do this, we will share your email address or phone number with the relevant social media partner. If you do not want us to use your personal information in this way we can only remove you from this by opting you out of all other marketing communications. If you wish to do this please contact us at [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk) or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate. 

Legal requirements \- in some circumstances, we may have to disclose your personal information by law, because a Court or the police or other law enforcement agency has requested it using the appropriate channels.

**Where in the world do we hold your information?**

Your data may occasionally be processed and held by third parties outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

Whereas in the UK and EEA, we implement a high standard of data protection law, some parts of the world do not implement such stringent laws. As a result, if we do send personal information overseas we will make sure that appropriate safeguards are in place to ensure it is protected in accordance with European data protection laws. These might include: -

·         Sending personal information only to countries that European Authorities have approved as having adequate data protection laws in place e.g. , Canada or Switzerland;

·         Sending personal data to organisations which are members of a scheme which has been approved by European Authorities as achieving adequate protection e.g. Privacy Shield; or

·         Entering into a standard form of contract with the recipient which European Authorities have approved as providing adequate protection.

If you want to know more about how we keep your data secure when it is transferred internationally, please contact us using [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk) or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate. 

**How long do we keep your information?**

We only hold your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide services to you unless there is a requirement to hold that information for a longer period – for example our insurers require us to hold certain information for certain periods of time, or we may be subject to a statutory obligation to keep hold of your information. 

If there is a possibility that you may have a legal claim against us, for example if you have had an accident in one of our Villages, or have made a complaint about a break with us, then we will hold your information for the duration of any statutory limitation period associated with such legal claims. 

As a result, the length of time that we keep your information for will vary depending on the purposes for which we have it. In any event, we will review what information we need on an ongoing basis and will only retain it for the minimum amount of time that we need it for, or are legally obliged to keep it for.

If you would like more information about how long your personal information will be held for, you can contact us at [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk "Email") or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate. 

**How secure is your information?**

 Our website is secured using TLS 1.2. This is the same level of security that all major UK banks use for their online banking, this means we encrypt every keystroke and mouse click on our website. All the data you provide us is held in our secure data centres which are further encrypted. We continue to review and amend our security practices to ensure we protect your data in this evolving security landscape.

Your data is important to us so please ensure you log out from our website if you are using a shared computer and never share your account information.

If at any point you suspect or become aware of a security incident (i.e. your password is stolen or you receive suspicious communication from someone holding themselves out to be a Center Parcs employee or from a dupe website claiming to be affiliated with Center Parcs), please forward the communication to us or report the incident by email to [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk "Email") or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate _ _ as soon as possible. If you have been the victim of a fraudulent transaction please always contact the police and/or your bank in the first instance to ensure your own finances are secure.

**What are your data protection rights?**

You have the right to request that we do not send marketing material to you and you can do this at any time by ticking the unsubscribe option in any communication we send you, by calling us on 0344 8267723 or by logging into your Center Parcs account. Please note it may take up to 28 days for the change to take effect.  

We will try to keep your personal information up to date but rely on you telling us promptly if your name, address, telephone number or any other details change. You can correct or amend your personal information by logging into your Center Parcs account or by contacting us on 0344 8267723. Equally, if you think any information we have about you is wrong or incomplete, please let us know by contacting us in the same way.

You also have the right to access your personal information and to receive a copy of it. You can exercise this right by emailing us at [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk) or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate, or by contacting us at Center Parcs, Legal Department, One Edison Rise, New Ollerton, Newark, Nottinghamshire, NG22 9DP.

New data protection laws also give you a number of additional rights including the right to request to have your personal data erased or transferred either to you or a third party in a commonly structured format and to have your personal information restricted. Please be aware that these latter rights only apply in limited circumstances and therefore even if you wish to exercise them, we may not always be required to comply.

For further information about how these rights apply, or to exercise your rights, please contact us on 0344 8267723 or email us at [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk) or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate.

**How do you make a complaint?**

If you do not think that we have processed your data in accordance with thispolicy, please contact us by email at [data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk](mailto:data.protection@centerparcs.co.uk) or at [data.protection@centerparcs.ie](mailto:dataprotection@centerparcs.ie) as appropriate. 

If you are in the UK you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner's Office. Information about how to do this is available at [www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/).

If you are in Ireland you have the right to complain to the Data Protection Commissioner. Information about how to do this is available at [www.dataprotection.ie](http://www.dataprotection.ie/)

**The Center Parcs Group**

The companies in the Center Parcs group covered by this privacy policy are listed below. Please note Center Parcs provides spa experiences under the "Aqua Sana" brand, this is a brand and not a separate legal entity:

· Center Parcs Limited, Company number: 01908230, Registered address: One Edison Rise, New Ollerton, Newark, Nottinghamshire, NG22 9DP

· Center Parcs (Operating Company) Limited, Company number: 04379585, Registered address: One Edison Rise, New Ollerton, Newark, Nottinghamshire, NG22 9DP

· CP Woburn (Operating Company) Limited, Company number: 07656412, Registered address: One Edison Rise, New Ollerton, Newark, Nottinghamshire, NG22 9DP

-  Center Parcs Ireland Limited, Company number: 554787, Registered address: 10 Earlsfort Terrace, Dublin 2, D02 T380, Ireland

Last updated: 21 May 2018.
